[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
You need to leave!
You have to get out of here!
Just to repeat myself!
I bought this space!
Therefore, you're trespassing! Get out!
[Mercedes] Madam.
Lily Cruz has the
people of Ardiente behind her.
It's about time we let her know
that you're not to be messed with.
-[Mateo] What is this?
-[Jaguar] Emilia Ardiente.
I just want you to know that she's mine.
If you want this partnership
to last, tell off your allies.
Who are you talking about?
-Why don't you ask Jaguar?
-Ma'am, sir! It's Mr. Arnaldo.
Why? What happened to my grandson?
-[Julio] Arnaldo? Arnaldo!
-[Emilia] Arnaldo.
Who are you?
[doctor] Arnaldo is suffering
from retrograde amnesia.
[reporter] Six condominium
buildings and a media complex
owned by Aguas Realty
were bombed earlier this morning
in what could be the deadliest
terrorist attack in recent memory.
Aguas Realty is done for,
and it's all your fault.
They may have destroyed our
buildings, but never our spirit.
We will rise again,
and we will be the symbol
of strength, courage, and hope.
[Julio] Whoever is behind these bombings
is giving Lily Cruz victory
on a silver platter!
Diego, do you remember
that woman at the construction site?
I believe she's our key
to finding out who's behind the bombings.
Any updates on what I told you to do?
Boss Jaguar, the bombing
of Aguas Realty was a clean job.
We still don't know
who's responsible for it,
but they used high-powered explosives.
I know one person
who could've masterminded…
a large-scale attack like that.
Boss Jaguar, I think the
Red Dragon is spitting out fire.
[tense music playing]
Has she contacted you again?
You may leave.
I'll call you again if I need anything.
[tense music intensifies]
Please call Arnaldo.
Yes, sir.
Governor. You called for me?
Yeah. I want you to monitor
Emilia very closely.
I suspect she's involved in the bombings
of Lily Cruz's properties.
I have this funny feeling
that my daughter
is hiding something from us.
-Yes, Governor.
-Thank you.
[laughing] He is so annoying!
You know, Papa just laughed
the whole thing off.
But I know Mama is involved
in the bombings.
I'd rather not comment on the issue.
That's a nice PR answer.
Can you at least, like,
blink once if it's a yes,
or blink twice if it's a no?
All I can say is that your mother
is paving the way for you.
So, just try to be
a little more patient, Emilia.
[clicks tongue] I'm an Ardiente.
Patience is a virtue.
Or should I say, a talent
that I never learned?
You are much more than an Ardiente, madam.
You're way, way more.
So, just try to be patient and trust me.
[inhales]
[exhales] Okay, I will try my best.
My very, very best.
[tense music playing]
[Julio] Hmm.
-Thank you.
-Arnaldo.
Sit down. Sit down, please.
Sure.
Uh… It's been a while
since we shared a meal together.
-[Arnaldo chuckles]
-And look at what we have.
So, let us partake of this full--
[Arnaldo sniffles]
-Amen. Yeah.
-Amen.
Um…
Yeah, as I was saying, um…
we have good food.
So, let's dig in.
Okay. [chuckles]
[Julio exhales]
You know, I…
I noticed a lot of changes
in you since you woke up
from your coma.
Um…
Is everything all right?
Is everything all right with you?
Uh… Of course, Grandpa.
Everything's all right.
I've never felt better.
You know, it's like a heavy load
was lifted from my heart.
[soft music playing]
I can't remember the past, but…
I'm excited about the future.
[clicks tongue] Now, that is good to hear,
that you're excited about the future.
[Arnaldo] Yes.
-So, um…
-[Arnaldo sniffles]
Just tell me when you feel you're ready,
so we can start planning
your return to politics.
Hmm.
Uh…
I want to quit politics, Grandpa.
Um… [clears throat]
Well… if you want to quit politics,
what do you want to do?
-Well, I want to be a priest.
-[chokes]
-Sir, are you okay?
-[Julio coughing]
Calm down. I'm okay. I'm okay.
[Julio clears throat]
-Are you okay? Sure?
-Yeah, yeah.
Yes, I'm--I'm okay.
-[clears throat]
-Okay.
-Let's eat.
-Yeah.
[sighs]
Remember Helena Montoya?
Yes. The philanthropist who
wants to invest in our company.
I want to review her proposal first.
Okay.
I also know an investor
who's interested
in investing in Aguas Realty.
Who?
I'll talk to them first,
then I'll give you the details.
They have to go through me, Mr. Paterno.
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
Miss Cruz…
I am not a freaking amateur.
I can handle this.
Mr. Paterno…
I don't think it would hurt for me…
to be cautious and inspect
every transaction we make here,
because I don't know who wants
to tear my company down.
-I know what I'm doing.
-No!
I want all the details about your investor
on my table tomorrow…
before the meeting begins.
[tense music playing]
Like what you said, Mr. Paterno,
you're not an amateur.
Details. Tomorrow.
[tense music intensifies]
Doc, you have to explain this to me.
Is my grandson ill, huh?
Why does he want to be a priest?
Is the kid really going nuts?
Your grandson is experiencing
dissociative fugue.
Because of his memory loss,
his brain is manifesting
a new consciousness to fill in the blanks.
It created a new identity…
that is totally different
from his inherent personality.
So, in short, my grandson
has really gone bonkers.
Doctor…
I've trained that child
since he was a little boy.
I trained him to be the fiercest
ruler among all Ardientes.
And now, this is what's
going to happen to him?
No! No. You have to help me, doc.
We need to bring the old Arnaldo back.
-[Arnaldo] Amen?
-[workers] Amen.
What? What was that?
[soft music playing]
[Arnaldo] Okay.
Next time, I'll read something
I'm sure that you'll all love.
-[Julio] Hey.
-Grandpa?
Um, good evening, Arnaldo.
[Arnaldo] Good evening.
All right, everybody, back to your posts.
Let's go.
Let's do this again next week. Okay?
Doc, we're good for now.
I'll talk to my grandson.
-Okay, Governor.
-Thank you.
Arnaldo…
I want you to stop preaching religion
to everyone here.
This isn't like you.
You're confusing them.
You have to return to your old self!
But I'm no longer the Arnaldo
-you once knew.
-[scoffs]
Grandpa, the old Arnaldo is gone.
The old has gone, and the new has come.
And right now, this is
the new Arnaldo, Grandpa.
Cut it out. The Arnaldo that I know…
is the mayor of Poblacion, Ardiente.
The Arnaldo that I remember is
someone I trained to be brave.
And when someone gets
in his way, he kills them.
You will go back to your old self,
to the Arnaldo that I remember.
So, you better stop this nonsense.
Or else, you'll see what I can do!
[dramatic music playing]
[phone chimes]
Hello?
[tense music playing]
Get ready for your next mission.
[tense music intensifies]
[thumps]
That Lily Cruz is so full of herself!
Who does she think she is? [sighs]
If I didn't owe so much to Prianka,
I would've left this company long ago.
To think, I'm trying to save this company!
She's such an ingrate.
So, what now?
Will you still give information
about your investor?
Me, give her information?
Of course not! You know what she'll do?
She'll get the investor
and take the credit!
[sighs]
[phone rings]
Excuse me. I need to answer this call.
Sure.
-[ringing continues]
-[sighs]
Mercedes?
Mr. Paterno. Have you talked to Lily Cruz?
Has our investment in
Aguas Realty been approved?
Uh… I'm sorry.
We just had a little trouble here.
But don't worry. I got you.
Just keep your word that
you'll invest a huge amount.
After all the bombings,
Aguas Realty is still a good investment.
The people still trust our company.
Very well then. My associate
will meet you tomorrow.
Will Lily Cruz be there?
Yes. Lily Cruz will be there.
I'll introduce your associate to her.
Good. Thank you, Mr. Paterno.
All right. Thanks.
We're in.
[tense music playing]
Jaguar, long time no see.
[distorted voice] What do you want?
Why did you call for me?
You have an upcoming mission.
The Red Dragon wants you to be ready.
Was Red Dragon the one
behind the Aguas Realty bombing?
Yes.
Why? What does she want from Lily Cruz?
You ask too many questions.
All you need to know right now
is that Red Dragon declared war
on Lily Cruz, and she needs
her best lieutenant --you.
[soft piano music playing]
Your lives are in danger, Camia.
I need to save you from the Red Dragon.
-[soft piano music playing]
-[water running]
[soft piano music playing]
Hello, everyone.
-Mr. Paterno isn't here?
-He isn't, Miss Cruz.
He's in a meeting with the investor today.
Meeting with the investor?
Did he at least send us
the investor's background?
-He didn't.
-He didn't send anything?
Nothing, ma'am.
[tense music playing]
You may go.
[tense music intensifies]
Excuse me. Miss Moran?
-Yes.
-Mr. Paterno.
-Hi.
-Come with me.
She's with me.
[line ringing]
[Mercedes] Hello.
I'm in now.
Good. Blow them up.
[suspenseful music playing]
-Mr. Paterno.
-Miss Cruz.
Um, I would like you to meet
Miss Mercedes' associate.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Lily] Diego, do you know that woman?
[Diego] Doesn't she work here?
[Lily] I think so. But all alone?
-[explosions]
-[screams]
You! Stop her!
[Lily] Stop her!
[suspenseful music playing]
[security officer 1] Hey!
[grunts]
[groans]
[grunting]
[Lily] Where did she go?
[suspenseful music playing]
-Hey!
-[Myla grunts]
You… You!
You're the one who blew up
the media complex!
That's right! It was me!
And I'm here to finish what I started!
[action music playing]
[both grunting]
[Lily groans]
[grunting]
[action music playing]
[Myla grunting]
[grunting]
[screams]
[both grunting]
[Myla groans]
Where's the bomb? Where's the bomb?!
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[Myla grunts]
[both grunting]
[grunting continues]
[breathes heavily]
[suspenseful music playing]
Hello?
Call the bomb squad,
and evacuate the building.
Do you understand?
Make sure everyone
gets out of this building!
[suspenseful music playing]
[clamoring]
[siren wailing]
[all screaming]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[bomb timer beeping]
[beeping continues]
-[laughs]
-[beeping continues]
[suspenseful music playing]
-[clamoring]
-[emergency alarm blaring]
-[emergency alarm ringing]
-[bomb timer beeping]
-[Myla laughing]
[Lily breathes heavily]
[bomb timer beeping]
[laughing]
-[emergency alarm blaring]
-[clamoring]
[bomb timer beeping]
[Myla laughing]
[breathes heavily]
-[panting]
-[Myla laughing]
-[groans]
-[laughing]
[both grunt]
Who do you work for? Who?!
Who is the bastard
who ordered you to do this?!
[laughing]
[Lily groans]
[Myla continues laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Myla laughing]
Make sure that woman doesn't escape.
We're here at the main office
of Aguas Realty,
where an alleged
terrorist threat was reported.
From what we've gathered,
someone carrying
a bomb infiltrated the building
-with the intention of…
-Lily.
…blowing Aguas Realty up. As of now,
all employees of Aguas Realty
have been evacuated.
And according to reports,
only the CEO, Miss Lily Cruz,
is still inside the said building.
Just recently, Miss Lily Cruz spoke up
regarding the consecutive bombings
of Aguas Realty properties,
But until now, the person or group
behind the bombings is still unidentified.
Well.
Looks like karma
is a bigger witch
than you are, Miss Lily Cruz.
[indistinct chatter]
The suspect, who snuck into Aguas Realty
with a bomb in her possession,
has now been arrested.
As for Miss Lily Cruz,
she seems unharmed.
[reporters clamor]
-Please do the interview later.
-Miss Lily Cruz.
-Make way.
I thought she was going to die.
I thought it was going
to be a happy ending.
[cop on TV] Please step aside.
[reporter] Miss Lily Cruz!
Your statement, please!
Please, stay back.
-You can interview them later.
-Miss Lily Cruz!
-Please stay back.
Do you know who's behind this?
Do you know who's behind all this, ma'am?
I wouldn't go against this enemy of yours.
[Julio] I hope he becomes a friend.
As the saying goes…
[speaks in Spanish]
"The enemy of my enemy…
is my friend."
[laughs]
[exhales deeply]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[Anna] Jepoy.
Where are you?
I just woke up, Anna.
[sighs] Something happened to Lily.
I know. Uh, I saw the news.
I thought you were asleep?
Yes, I was, but I woke up
and saw the news just now.
All right.
We're on our way to Lily's
house. You should come too.
Okay, Anna.
I'll talk to you later.
I'll be there, okay?
You guys go ahead. I'll meet you there.
Be careful.
[mockingly] "Be careful."
[laughs] You're funny.
I'll really be careful.
And where are you going?
I'm going to Anna. They need me.
No! You're not going anywhere.
You're staying with me.
-Let go of me.
-You're my little puppy dog.
Pup--What?!
I'm not your little pet!
So, don't strangle me!
Use me all you want, but remember this…
You can't control me.
-Okay.
-Where's my shirt?
Well, you're so cute. Why are you so mad?
I want you to stay, my little puppy dog.
[Natalie] Hmm?
How can I make you stay? Hmm?
How about 10 million pesos?
Ma'am, remember this too.
You can't buy me!
Okay.
For each of the heads of the Ardientes?
There you go. Those are
my little puppy dog eyes.
So, what do you say, champion?
Will you do that for mommy?
Hmm?
[tense music playing]
Governor, we still have
no intel as to who's responsible
for the consecutive bombings
against Aguas Realty.
It's because you're lacking intelligence!
Wait, can you even spell "intelligence"?
You know, I'll give you a bonus.
Spell "smart", instead.
Emilia, will you just please shut up?
Because if you've got nothing
to add to our conversation,
keep your trap shut.
Why, Papa?
Are you assuming I don't know
anything about this?
Well?
Diego, has Lily called you?
Not yet, Auntie.
Auntie, don't worry. I'm sure she's safe.
Mom?
-Lily, dear.
-[Diego] Lily.
Lily, are you hurt?
-[Diego] You're wounded.
-It's just a scratch, Mom.
I'm fine.
What happened to the bomber?
Diego, do you remember
the woman we saw at the construction site?
-Yeah.
-I was right.
My hunch was right.
She was the one who bombed my buildings.
The police have her now
and are interrogating her.
I'm sure they'll be
on their way here to update us
with whatever information
they can get from her.
Who could she be working for?
No one else could've done this
except the Ardientes.
[tense music playing]
[Julio] Oh, really now?
So, you're telling me you know
who's behind all of this?
No.
I rest my case.
[Diego] The Ardientes may be violent,
but they don't have any power left.
This isn't new to us, Diego.
They're desperate.
When the Ardientes get crippled,
they become more violent.
[tense music playing]
Well, what if…
[laughs]
-What's so funny, Papa?
-[Julio continues laughing]
Nothing. It just crossed my mind.
Is it possible that you're
responsible for all this chaos?
No, no, no.
The thought that your mind can come up
with a plan this big is…
-It's a ridiculous concept!
-[both laughing]
[Julio continues laughing]
-[clears throat]
-[Julio laughing]
[laughing continues]
[laughs on the inside] Laugh now, Papa.
If I'm right in thinking that my
real mother is behind all this,
I'll be the one laughing.
And my laugh will be
even more annoying than yours.
[Julio laughing]
[tense music playing]
[Diego] Tea?
[soft piano music playing]
I envy Lily and Diego.
They're always there for each other.
It's because Lily can
trust Diego completely
because he's not hiding any secrets.
How can you be so sure?
[sighs] Why are you hiding that anyway?
What are you talking about?
What exactly is that mark on your neck?
I was shooting a gun.
The bullet bounced back,
and I got burned by the gunpowder.
-Gunpowder, huh? Let me see.
-Mm-hm.
This? You see this?
-What?
-Yeah, right there.
You know what, Jepoy? It suits you.
But I wish your face were covered in it,
so I'd never see it again.
We already have so many problems.
How could you still play around?!
Was it fun? Did it feel good?
Huh?
[somber music playing]
How about 10 million pesos?
For each of the heads of the Ardientes?
I've spoken with the police.
Myla Lomeda, 23 years old.
A resident of Tondo.
[sighs] She was on a suicide mission.
She risked her life just
so could blow up that building.
The police said she still refuses to talk.
But I won't stop until I get information.
I'm going to investigate
and find out who's behind all this.
[tense music playing]
Hello, my new friend.
How are you?
What do you want, Emilia?
[clicks tongue] I came here
because I wanted to know
if Mama had anything to do
with the bombing at Aguas Realty,
and if she had anything
to do with my appointment
as the new governor's consultant.
[laughs]
And just why would she do that?
[laughing sarcastically]
Because I'm her daughter!
If she helped me before,
I'm sure she'd help me again now.
You'll find out soon enough.
When it's the right time.
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
-Hi, Lily, Auntie.
-Hey, Anna.
-I'll get you some food.
-Oh.
No need, Auntie. I already ate.
I just dropped by
to let you know I'm off to work
at Lily's teaching program.
Where's Jepoy?
I don't think I saw him leave.
Did he stay here for the night?
Oh, just let him be.
He was in a bad mood last night
when I talked to him.
He'll come back eventually.
Well, in that case, I'll have
my bodyguards go with you.
Just to be safe.
Okay, Lily. Thanks.
-You sure you won't eat, Anna?
-I'm fine.
Myla still refuses to talk.
We can't let things end here.
If that Myla still refuses to talk…
then we'll gather information on our own.
We're going to take the initiative, Diego.
[tense music playing]
[Julio laughing]
That's what you get for picking on me!
-Papa.
-It's a beautiful day!
Good morning! Good morning, Emilia!
It really is a good morning, Papa.
Did you kill someone today?
You've got such a devilish smile.
No, no, no. Better!
Someone is messing up Lily Cruz's life!
-[laughs]
-And that can't get any better.
-[laughs] See? See?
-I know.
You're laughing. You're enjoying it.
[laughs] I know. It's a really
beautiful day, Papa.
Yes. Okay, let's have breakfast.
Yes. But you're just going to have fruits.
Sir. Ma'am.
-Yes?
-Sir Arnaldo's…
gone missing from his room.
How could he go missing?! Find him!
Yes, sir.
[suspenseful music playing]
Of all the--Where the hell
did that boy go to now?!
Papa, he could be anywhere. Do something!
Governor, we've searched
the premises. He isn't here.
I can't accept that.
If he's not here, then look outside.
Order all our men to move, if you have to!
Governor, we don't have
full access to that, as of now.
I don't care!
I want you to scour every
corner of our province…
before the enemy finds
Arnaldo and kills him!
Enemies like Lily Cruz,
Madrigal, and Diego Torillo!
-Yes, sir.
-[Julio] Go!
[sighs]
[groans]
[footsteps departing]
[exhales]
Lily, dear.
Mom?
Why not just leave this to the police?
I'm sorry, Mom,
but I have to do this myself.
Then bring security with you, okay?
We will, Mom.
-Be careful.
-Yes, Mom.
-You too, Diego.
-Yes, Auntie.
-We need to go, Mom.
-Okay.
[door opens]
-[door closes]
-[sighs]
[tense music playing]
-[busy tone]
-[sighs]
What's wrong with that woman?
Of course she has to be busy
when we actually have to talk.
Annoying.
[busy tone]
Duh!
Hmm.
Madam, we cleaned the mess.
[ominous music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
Stay here and keep watch.
[door opens]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[suspenseful music continues]
[somber music playing]
Diego, don't.
Here.
He's dead. He was strangled.
We'll report this to the police
later, anonymously.
But for now, let's hurry up
and find a lead.
Okay.
[suspenseful music playing]
[door closes]
Well? What's the update?
Sir, we couldn't find him.
We've already searched the entire house.
He's not around? Then what
are you still doing here?!
Go out and search for him! Move it!
Papa, I've called my contacts to help.
[laughs]
This is a surprise. You have contacts?
[Emilia scoffs] Cut it out, Papa!
The one time we need to find Arnaldo,
you're basically powerless.
And now what? What can you do? Nothing!
-Shut up, Emilia!
-I am not gonna shut up, Papa!
That's the truth!
You are no longer in position,
so that's why you can't do anything now!
Papa! Emilia, that's enough!
You know what?
I'll just approach someone
who can truly help us!
Hey! Where are you going?!
To Governor Mateo Ruiz.
He's the governor right now, isn't he?
And not you!
[tense music playing]
Emilia!
What?! That hurts!
[laughs]
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
We can use these.
Mercedes Palacio?
[tense music intensifies]
[Lily] Mr. Paterno's dead.
We need to be cautious, Mom.
I'm not dealing with just anybody here.
But I got a lead. Mercedes Palacio.
[Damian] These people are
on a different level.
-She can't win this.
-Why, Damian?
Do you know Mercedes Palacio?
Find Arnaldo.
Search every corner of Ardiente.
Mayor.
-[grunts] What did I ever do to you?!
-I don't know what--
[Jepoy] Why do you have to hurt
everyone I love?!
[Arnaldo] I don't know you!
[Jepoy] As long as
the Ardientes are around,
our lives are in danger, Diego.
[Mercedes] The time has come.
Your real mother wants to see you.
[Lily] I've been to hell and back.
There's no way I'll ever be afraid of you!
[theme music playing]